<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="moving_out_title">Goodbye WarmShowers!</string>
    <string name="moving_out_subtitle">message from developers</string>
    <string name="moving_out_message"><![CDATA[
        Dear Fellow WS Community Member,<br/>
        <br/>
        We are a group of bike tourers and developers, former WarmShowers.org volunteers. We created this app for you as much as for ourselves. For years, this was the official WS app, trusted by thousands of people.<br/>
        <br/>
        Back in 2012, when this app was created, WarmShowers was an open, free and welcoming platform. Since 2015, under the new board, WS has been slowly but steadily moving in the direction that <b>we can’t agree with any more</b>. (*) It’s time for us to go our own way.<br/>
        <br/>
        We are thinking about creating <b>a new platform</b> dedicated for the worldwide community of bicycle touring travelers and those who want to host them. One that is again <b>built on trust and openness</b>, that reflects values which drive people to open doors to their homes and welcome strangers traveling the world by bicycle. One that helps to build lifelong friendships that cross boundaries. <b>Free and transparent</b> for everyone forever.<br/>
        <br/>
        Please <b>help us by <a href="https://warmshowers.github.io/wsandroid/survey">filling out this short survey</a></b>. We would like to understand which aspects are important to you for a bicycle touring platform.<br/>
        <br/>
        Until we get <a href="https://fedihospex.github.io">something new</a> working, we hope to meet you in the <a href="https://www.trustroots.org/?circle=cyclists">Cyclists Circle at trustroots.org</a> (focus on cultural exchange) or on <a href="https://WelcomeToMyGarden.org">WelcomeToMyGarden.org</a> (focus on slow travelers).<br/>
        <br/>
        See you on the road!<br/>
        <br/>
        Yours,<br/>
        Former WS Android volunteers<br/>
        <br/>
        <br/>
        ----<br/>
        <br/>
        <br/>
        <i>A last shoutout to all the people who <a href="https://github.com/warmshowers/wsandroid">contributed to this app</a> in the past 9&nbsp;years: <br/>
        @jstaffans, @rfay, @jeanfrancoisbeaulieu, @CyrilWendl, @kirbycool, @saemy, @siavash1986, @LaurentSouchet-Orange, @PattaFeuFeu, @sgelb, @dproctor, @Poussinou, @noSim, @mariha, @cioccasimone97, @jakobhanna, @nonno.<br/>
        Thank you!</i>
    ]]></string>

    <string name="moving_out_backstory_title">(*) Backstory</string>
    <string name="moving_out_backstory_body"><![CDATA[
        Warmshowers started life as an openly available contact list of cyclists committed to sharing their love of bicycle touring and their hospitality.<br/>
        <br/>
        In 2001, this list was moved online by Randy Fay to help expand its reach and welcome more people into the bicycle touring family. And for almost 15 years he maintained this service with an open and welcoming attitude that made Warmshowers what it is today. Volunteers helped create an iPhone app and in 2012, an Android app so that cyclists could benefit from Warmshowers on the move.<br/>
        <br/>
        In 2015, the Warmshowers Foundation was created to help manage the growing service and secure its future in light of Randy’s retirement. Sadly, the board from the outset did not share the volunteers’ open and inclusive attitude that made Warmshowers so well-loved.<br/>
        <br/>
        Decisions that had previously been made with community support were removed from the public forum. Volunteers that helped grow Warmshowers were pushed out and unable to contribute. And donations that used to support the operating costs were funnelled into private software companies who haven’t published or made any significant upgrades in over 5 years.<br/>
        <br/>
        In 2021, the Warmshowers board finally declared the old community driven apps a security hazard. Instead of helping them upgrade, it has withdrawn the Android app’s access and blocked the developers’ accounts, favouring the paid app built by the aforementioned software companies with a $20 a year subscription model.<br/>
        <br/>
        So here we are, with the story of how a once welcoming and open platform has become a closed subscription service, locking out the very community it supports.<br/>
        <br/>
        See also: <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Warm_Showers#History">WarmShowers History</a>, <i>Wikipedia</i>
    ]]></string>

    <string name="moving_out_what_to_do_title">What else can I do?</string>
    <string name="moving_out_what_to_do_body"><![CDATA[
        <ul>
          <li>&nbsp;Make your Warmshowers friends aware of this situation by writing them a message and/or updating your profile text. You can refer to <a href="https://warmshowers.bike">https://WarmShowers.bike</a>.</li>
          <br/>
          <li>&nbsp;See what we are working on right now - <a href="https://fedihospex.github.io">a federation of hospitality exchange platforms</a>. On that basis, we hope to build new next generation bicycle touring hospitality app (and many others!).</li>
          <br/>
          <li>&nbsp;Check for <a href="https://warmshowers.bike">updates from us</a> or join our Facebook group <a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/243374777243989">Open Alternative to WarmShowers.org</a>.</li>
          <br/>
          <li>&nbsp;Check other hospitality exchange platforms: <a href="https://bewelcome.org">BeWelcome.org</a>, <a href="https://couchers.org/">Couchers.org</a>, <a href="https://cycleplanet.org/">CyclePlanet.org</a>.</li>
          <br/>
          <li>&nbsp;<a href="https://www.warmshowers.org/contact">Contact the Warmshowers board</a> to tell them how you feel about the direction they have taken.</li>
          <br/>
          <li>&nbsp;<a href="market://details?id=fi.bitrite.android.ws">Rate this app</a> for it to get more attention.</li>
        </ul>
    ]]></string>

    <string name="moving_out_notification_title" translatable="false">@string/moving_out_title</string>
    <string name="moving_out_notification_text_short">A message from the former developers</string>
    <string name="moving_out_notification_text_long">Read what\'s happening with Warmshowers.</string>
</resources>
